sql-server-performance.com 2006-11-10

# SQL-Server-Performance.Com Privacy Policy

Privacy Statement

* * *

SQL-Server-Performance.Com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices of SQL-Server-Performance.Com. 

We collect the default information that is sent from your browser to our website when you visit, which includes, but is not limited to: dynamic information, click-stream information, http information, and search terms. We summarize the information we collect, but do not maintain individual records about our visitors. We use this information to help us better understand our website's visitors. This summarized information is used internally by us and our advertisers. 

Our website, including some of the outside services we use, uses cookies. If you have a question about cookies, please contact us. Our members-only forum does collect some _optional_ private information, but this information is never shared with outside parties, other than that which is displayed on the member's profile page (which is optional information and under control of the member). 

This site contains links to other sites, including sponsors. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. You will need to check with these website directly to view their privacy policies. 

This privacy statement is subject to change without notice. 

Disputes arising in connection with the privacy statement will be resolved by our web site's customer service representative. Errors or wrongful actions arising in connection with our privacy policy can be remedied by contacting: [webmaster@sql-server-performance.com](mailto:webmaster@sql-server-performance.com).

E-Mail Newsletter 

If you subscribe to our e-mail newsletter, we will not give or sell your e-mail address to anyone. To unsubscribe from our newsletter, see the instructions at the bottom of your most recent newsletter. We will make a mailing on behalf of our advertisers to our mailing list, but we never share our the e-mail addresses with them. If you don't want to receive these sponsored mailings, you must unsubscribe from our newsletter. As an alternative to unsubscribing to your newsletter, if you don't want to receive any special mailings, but you want to receive the newsletter, you can set your spam filter to reject any mailing from [ sponsor@sql-server-performance.com](mailto:sponsor@sql-server-performance.com), but accept any mailing from [ webmaster@sql-server-performance.com](mailto:webmaster@sql-server-performance.com), which is the e-mail address that the newsletter is sent from.

Contests 

From time to time we run contests on our website. The winner's e-mail addresses are listed in our newsletter as the winners. If you don't want your e-mail address published if you are a winner, you must contact us before you become a winner in order for us not to list your e-mail address.

Contacting Our Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this website, you can contact: 

_[Brad M. McGehee](mailto:webmaster@sql-server-performance.com)  
SQL-Server-Performance.Com  
188 Cricket LN  
Rogersville, MO 65742_
